Hey,you guys ever wonder why they call it "Thanksgiving"?
你們有想過 為什麼要叫感恩節嗎？
Okay. Hey,Monica,you're doing Thanksgiving next week,right?
好，摩妮卡 你下星期要煮感恩節大餐吧？
Because Carol's taking Ben to her parents' place in Florida.
卡蘿要帶班去佛州看她父母
Okay,okay. I'll make Thanksgiving dinner.
好好好，我來煮
You don't have to beg.
你不必求我
I didn't beg. I just asked once.
我沒有求你，我只是問你
You could beg,you know.
求一下又不會死
Monica said I could make dessert this year.
摩妮卡說我今年可以做甜點
-You're gonna cook something? -Hey,I cook.
你要下廚？ 我會下廚啊
Offering people gum is not cooking.
拿口香糖給別人不叫下廚
Are you sure Monica said you could cook this year?
摩妮卡真的是說今年嗎？
I remember her saying in two years. You said in two years,right?
我記得她是說後年 你是說後年吧？
No,I promised her.
我已經答應她了
Are you sure you want to start out with something as big as Thanksgiving dinner?
你確定要一出手 就做感恩節甜點？
I mean,maybe you wanna try a little Thanksgiving breakfast?
要不要先做感恩節早餐？
Maybe a Thanksgiving snack?
或是感恩節零食？
Come on,you guys, I can do this.
別這樣，我一定行
Remember,I made those peanut butter cookies.
我不是做過花生醬餅乾？
What are you guys so worried about? Cooking is easy.
你們在擔心什麼 煮菜很簡單
You just follow the recipe.
照食譜就對了
If it says,"boil two cups of salt," you just boil two cups of salt.
如果食譜說「將兩杯鹽煮沸」 你就把兩杯鹽煮沸
The One Where Ross Got High
本集播出：「感恩的季節」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Okay,great. Bye.
太好了，再見
Guess who's coming to Thanksgiving dinner?
你猜誰要來吃感恩節晚餐？
Sidney Poitier?
薜尼鮑迪？ （曾主演「誰來晚餐」）
I miss Rachel.
我懷念瑞秋
My parents.
是我爸媽
Great, they haven't seen the place since I moved in.
太好了，我搬進來之後 他們還沒來過
If you could not mention that we live together, that'd be great.
對，要是你能不提同居的事 就太好了
I was thinking we'd eat around 4.
我打算4點左右開動
Why can't I tell them we live together?
為什麼不能提同居的事？
They don't know we're dating. Should we eat in the kitchen?
因為他們不知道我們在交往 要在廚房吃嗎？
Why haven't you told them?
你為什麼沒有告訴他們？
Well,I was going to. I really was.
我本來要說，真的
But then somewhere, just out of nowhere,I didn't.
但是後來不知怎的就沒說了
Why not? Wouldn't they be happy?
你為什麼沒說？ 他們不會開心嗎？
So,dinner in the kitchen around 4. I'll see you then.
4點左右廚房開動，到時候見
Why wouldn't they be happy?
他們為什麼不會開心？
Well,because...
因為…
mainly...
主要是
they don't like you.
他們不喜歡你
-I'm sorry. -What? Why? Why?
對不起 什麼？為什麼？
Maybe because you used to be aloof...
也許是因為你以前很冷漠
or that you're sarcastic or that you joke around...
很尖酸刻薄，老愛開玩笑
or that you throw your clothes on the couch.
或許是因為你脫了衣服都亂丟
Is this why they don't like me or you don't like me?
這是他們的還是你的看法
I know I should have told them. I shouldn't care what they think.
我知道我應該告訴他們 我不該在意他們
I'm sorry.
對不起
It'll be okay because when they come over, I will be charming.
其實沒關係，等他們來了 我會表現得很迷人
I will make them love me, then we'll tell them.
我會讓他們愛上我 然後我們再說
Will that work?
你真的覺得可行？
I can be pretty charming,babe. I won you over, didn't l?
我也可以很有魅力 我不就贏得了你的心？
I don't think you'll ever get my parents that drunk.
你應該不能把他們灌到那麼醉
Hey. Oh, good,Ross. Your parents like me, right?
太好了，羅斯 你爸媽喜歡我，對吧？
Yes, of course they like you.
他們當然喜歡你
Monica told me they don't.
摩妮卡說他們不喜歡我
Yeah,they don't like you.
對，他們不喜歡你
Do you know why?
你知道原因嗎？
Maybe it's because you're sarcastic or maybe it's because you..
也許是因為你很尖酸刻薄 或者是因為…
If people don't know, they shouldn't just guess!
不知道就不要亂猜
Another Thanksgiving with nothing to give thanks for.
帥啊 又一個不值得感恩的感恩節
Maybe I give thanks for you shutting up,huh?
也許我可以感恩你閉嘴
Maybe I give thanks by taking my PlayStation to my place.
也許我可以感恩你把我的電動 送去我的新家
Maybe I love you.
也許我愛你
Hey,guys.
你們好
No,I don't want to play video games, Joey!
不要，我不想打電動
Are you guys going to Chandler's for Thanksgiving?
你們要去錢德家過感恩節嗎？
Yeah,why?
對，怎麼了？
Me and my friends are doing Thanksgiving uptown.
我和幾個舞者朋友想一起慶祝
I thought you might like to come.
我想說你們可能想去
For real?
真的去？
You should go to Chandler's. None of us can cook.
你們是該去錢德家 我們沒有人會做菜
We'll just drink all day.
最後八成都在喝酒
We go to yours!
好，我們去
We have to stop across the hall because it's my sister.
對，我們得過去露個面 畢竟她是我妹妹
But,you know,actually, growing up with a sister was nice...
不過有個妹妹是好事
because it helped me understand women.
讓我很瞭解女人心
Yeah, you should tell your friends that.
你應該告訴她們
Okay.
好
How you got three women to marry you, I'll never know.
真不知你怎麼能騙到三個老婆
Hey,Mon,look. I'm melting butter.
摩妮卡，你看，我在融化奶油
That's great,Rach. You now have the cooking skills of a hot day.
太好了，跟天氣熱的效果一樣
Phoebe,check it out! For my dessert...
菲比，你看，感恩節甜點
I'm making a traditional English trifle.
我決定做酒果醬鬆糕
Wow. That sounds great! And what are you making,Monica?
聽起來好棒 摩妮卡你呢？
In case Rachel's dessert is so good that I eat all of it...
萬一瑞秋的甜點 好吃到被我吃光光
and there's none left for anybody else!
別人會沒得吃
Nothing.
我不做
Nothing?
你不做？
No,sweetie. I trust you.
對，我信任你
If I mess this up, there's nothing else for dessert?
所以要是我搞砸 就沒有甜點了？
You won't mess it up.
你不會搞砸的
I love that. You really have faith in me. Thank you.
摩妮卡，我好高興 你真的對我有信心，謝謝
Question: How do you know when the butter is done?
技術問題 這些奶油什麼時候好？
It's done about two minutes before it looks like that.
大約變成這樣2分鐘前
-The food smells great, Mon. -And the place looks so nice.
菜聞起來好香 這裡佈置得真漂亮
-Hey,happy Thanksgiving,everybody! -Happy Thanksgiving!
感恩節快樂
-Well,this has been great. -See you.
真是開心 再見
Whoa,whoa,whoa!
Where you going?
你們要去哪裡？
We did say we'd stop by this little thing Joey's roommate is having.
我們說過要去參加 喬伊的室友的聚會
Oh,Janine, the really hot dancer girl?
火辣舞者吉寧？
Some would say she's attractive,yes.
有些人會說她很有魅力
Who else is going to be there?
還有誰會去？
Her friends.
她的幾個朋友
Her dancer friends?
舞者朋友？
Yes! All right?
對啦，好不好？
All of her hot dancer friends are gonna be there...
她的性感舞者朋友都會去
and they'll be drinking and dancing and we really want to go!
她們會喝酒跳舞 我們真的很想去
Dude,we were good.
都快成功了
You're not going. You said you'd eat here and you'll eat here.
你們哪兒也不准去 你們說要來吃飯就別想跑
Yeah,and leaving us to go see hot dancer girls...
扔下我們去看性感舞者
is not very Thanksgiving-y.
可不太感恩
Oh,but it is.
但是...
It's like the first Thanksgiving when the Indians and Pilgrims sat down.
第一個感恩節就是這樣 印地安人和清教徒共進晚餐
Then the Indians taught the Pilgrims...
然後印地安人告訴清教徒
...what it meant to be hot in the New World!
新世界的性感定義是什麼
Fellas,I really think you should stay here.
我真的覺得你們應該留下來
You're just jealous because you can't go.
你不能去就嫉妒
That is so not true.
沒有這回事
-Hello,everybody! -Hi!
大家好
Hi,Dad. Mom.
爸，媽
Look! Look who it is! It's Chandler!
看，是錢德耶
Oh,yes,of course. Hello,Chandler.
錢德，你好
Mr. and Mrs. Geller, you look wonderful.
伯父伯母，你們的氣色真好
It is great to have you here. Let us take your coats.
歡迎，外套給我們吧
Whoa,it snowing out there?
外面在下雪嗎？
No.
沒有
Monica,all this food looks wonderful.
摩妮卡，菜看起來都好好吃
You should do this for a living.
你應該考慮走這一行
Okay,I have dandruff. There's no need to laugh and point.
就算我有頭皮屑 你也不必指著我笑
Chandler was laughing at your joke.
爸，錢德是在笑你的笑話
My joke wasn't funny.
我的笑話又不好笑
Chandler laughs at everything.
錢德什麼事都笑
That's one of the great things about him.
那是他的優點之一
Rach,I just remembered.
瑞秋，我剛剛想到
I had a dream about Mr. Geller last night.
我昨晚夢到蓋勒先生
Really?
真的嗎？
I dreamt that he saved me from a burning building...
對，我夢到他把我從火場救出
and he was so brave and so strong.
他好英勇好強壯
And it's making me look at him totally differently.
我對他完全改觀
He used to be just "Jack Geller,Monica and Ross' dad."
他以前只是傑克蓋勒 摩妮卡和羅斯的爸爸
Now he's "Jack Geller,dream hunk."
現在他是傑克蓋勒，夢中情人
I don't know. To me, he'll always be "Jack Geller...
不知道耶 對我來說他永遠都是傑克蓋勒
walks in while you're changing."
在你換衣服時闖進來
You know,Dad,Chandler is one of Ross' very best friends.
爸 錢德是羅斯最要好的朋友之一
Yes,I know.
是，我知道
Ross sure is a great guy.
羅斯是個好青年
I've always felt that how a man turns out...
我一直覺得兒子...
is a reflection on his father.
是父親的翻版
I always thought that too. Tell me, what does your father do?
我也有同感 請問你爸是做什麼的？
He's a headliner of a...
他是...
gay burlesque show.
同志歌舞秀的頭牌
You're killing us. Will you serve the dessert already?
瑞秋你急死人了，快上甜點啦
There's drunken dancers a-waiting!
有酒醉的舞者都在等我們
Look at it. Isn't it beautiful?
你們看，很漂亮吧？
Yeah. What is it?
是啊，這是什麼？
It's a trifle. It's got all these layers.
酒果醬鬆糕，有很多層
First there's a layer of ladyfingers,then jam...
先是一層小鬆糕，然後是果醬
then custard, which I made from scratch...
然後是我自己做的乳蛋糕
then raspberries, more ladyfingers...
然後是覆盆子 然後又是小鬆糕
then beef sauteed with peas and onions...
然後是豌豆洋蔥炒嫩牛肉
then a little bit more custard...
然後又有一點乳蛋糕
then bananas and then I put whipped cream on top.
然後是香蕉 最後再塗上鮮奶油
What was the one right before bananas?
香蕉前面是什麼？
The beef. Yeah,that was weird to me too.
炒牛肉嗎？我也覺得有點奇怪
But then I thought, "Well,there's minced-meat pie."
不過我想說連甜肉餡餅都有了
That's an English dessert.
那是一種英式甜點
These people just put strange things in their food.
英國人都放一堆怪東西
Can I borrow rum from your place?
對了，可以跟你借蘭姆酒嗎？
Yeah,sure.
當然可以
While I'm gone, don't you sneak a taste.
我不在的時候你們可別偷吃
Beef in a dessert?
甜點加牛肉？
No,no,no. There is no way.
不可能的
I know. And only one layer of jam?
就是啊，而且果醬才一層
What is up with that?
有沒有搞錯？
Oh,my God.
天哪
The pages are stuck together.
這兩頁黏在一起
Chandler!
錢德
Oh,my God. She made half an English trifle and...
天哪，她做了酒果醬鬆糕加…
half a shepherd's pie!
肉餡馬鈴薯泥餅
Man,now she's gonna start all over.
完了，她得重做了
We're never gonna get to introduce the hot girls to the New World.
我們沒辦法帶那些辣妹 認識新世界了
No,no,we will. We just won't tell her she messed up.
不，我們可以 不要告訴她就是了
Just let her serve the beef-custard thing?
然後讓她上那個牛肉乳蛋糕？
Yeah. It'll be like a funny Thanksgiving story.
對，這會是個有趣的回憶
Vomiting stories are funny,I guess.
嘔吐的回憶的確很有趣
Joey. God,your apartment is,like,100 degrees.
喬伊，天哪，你家熱死了
Did it make you want to walk around in your underwear?
你會不會想脫到只剩內衣？
No.
不會
Still not hot enough!
還不夠熱
Rachel. Okay,look at him.
瑞秋？ 怎樣？
Look at those strong hands.
你看他，你看那雙有力的手
Oh,what I wouldn't give to be that can of condensed milk.
我真想當那瓶…煉乳
Chandler was just saying how beautiful your sweater is.
媽，錢德說你的毛衣很好看
Thank you. I just bought it.
謝謝你，這是新衣服
Yes,well,it's very beautiful and it's cream-colored and tight and...
是嗎，很漂亮，米色的，很緊
I don't mean tight. It's not tight. Not that I was looking at...
我不是指很緊，不會很緊 我沒有在看…
What's the matter with him?
他是怎麼搞的？
I think he's stoned again.
大概又嗑藥了
What?
什麼？
I need to talk to you.
我有事要告訴你
I think I might know why my parents don't like you.
我大概知道 我爸媽為什麼不喜歡你了
Why?
是嗎？為什麼？
Okay,remember we were young.
記不記得我們年輕的時候
Spring break, sophomore year, I got high in my bedroom...
大二的春假，我在房裡哈麻
and my parents walked in and smelled it...
我爸媽走進來聞到了
so I told them that you had gotten stoned and jumped out the window.
於是我就說你哈了麻 跳窗走了
Why did you do that?
什麼？你為什麼要賴給我？
I don't know. Yours was the first name that popped into my head.
我不知道，我第一個想到你
I didn't think it'd matter.
對不起，我以為不會怎樣
How could it not matter?
怎麼可能不會怎樣？
How was I to know we'd be friends after college...
我怎麼知道我們會變成死黨
and you'd be living with my sister?
更別提你會跟我妹同居了
What about the "friends forever" stuff?
那些「生死之交」的豪語呢？
I don't know. I was all high.
不曉得，我當時正high
Mom and Dad sent me to find out if you were trying to get Ross stoned.
爸媽叫我來看看 你是不是想找羅斯嗑藥
Your parents caught Ross smoking pot in college,and he blamed it on me!
羅斯大學哈麻被他們逮到 他居然賴給我
I can't believe you!
羅斯，你怎麼這樣
We haven't told them we're together because they hate me, so fix this.
他們討厭我，我們才沒公開
Okay, okay, I'll tell them it wasn't Chandler who got high.
好啦，我會說哈麻的不是錢德
Now, who should I say it was?
那我要說是誰？
You! It's not like it's a big deal. You don't still do it or anything.
你！這又沒什麼 你現在又沒在嗑藥
All right. Now,who should I say tricked me into doing it?
好啦好啦 那我要說是誰騙我這麼做的？
Nobody. You're gonna go out there and tell them exactly what happened.
沒有人，你要跟他們說實話
-Really? -Yes!
是嗎？ 對
Okay.
好吧
Wait,is there anything else I should know?
等等，還有別的事嗎？
No.. Oh,yeah....
沒了…喔有…
You microwaved a bunch of my dad's records.
你把我爸的一堆唱片拿去微波
Why?
為什麼？
Evidently,you weren't very good at handling your high.
顯然你一high就會很失控
Dad, please don't pick your teeth out here.
爸，請別在這裡剔牙
And if you're gonna put your feet up..
如果你要翹腳，怎麼不坐…
Leave him alone!
摩妮卡，不要煩他
Will you hurry up?
你快點好嗎？
Did you not hear me when I told you that Janine's friends are dancers?
你之前沒聽到我說 吉寧的朋友都是舞者嗎？
And that they're gonna be drinking a lot?
而且她們會喝很多酒？
No,I did. But tell me again because it's so romantic.
我是聽到了，不過你再說一次 好浪漫喔
You're whipping so slow. Do it faster!
你打得好慢，不能快一點嗎？
I don't want to make any mistakes!
喬伊，我不想犯錯
If I screw it up, everybody's gonna be like:
甜點只有這一道，要是我搞砸
"Oh,remember that Thanksgiving when Rachel screwed up the trifle?"
大家會說「記得那次感恩節」 「瑞秋把酒果醬鬆糕做壞了」
Just let me worry about making it, and you just worry about eating it.
所以做讓我來做 你只管擔心吃的部分
Oh,I am.
我是很擔心
-If you don't tell them, then I will. -Okay. Fine.
羅斯，你再不說，我就要說了 好啦
Ross, can I talk to you for a second?
羅斯，你可以來一下嗎？
Can it wait? I have to tell my parents something.
等一下好嗎？ 我有事要告訴我爸嗎
No,it can't? Okay.
不能等？好吧
We have to tell Rachel she messed up her dessert.
我覺得我們應該告訴瑞秋 她做錯了
What? What is with everybody?
什麼？大家是都怎麼了？
It's Thanksgiving,not...
今天是感恩節，不是...
Truth Day!
告解日
Look,when everyone eats that banana-meat thing...
等大家吃到那道香蕉肉甜點
they'll all make fun of her. Do you want that?
一定會取笑她，那樣你也好嗎
We'll just get everyone to act like they like it.
好，我們就叫大家假裝喜歡
That way,no one makes fun of her...
那樣就不會有人取笑她
and we still get to go to sweet-potato pie.
我們也可以去找那些小辣椒
Dude,they're not objects.
別把她們物化
Just kidding. I'll talk to them. You distract her.
開玩笑的，我去告訴大家 你把瑞秋拖開
Hey,Rach,can I talk to you outside for a sec?
瑞秋，可以出去談一下嗎？
Okay.
好吧
What's up,Ross?
什麼事？
So....
所以…
Thanksgiving.
感恩節
The holiday season is upon us.
歲末季節又來了
And...
是啊
you look nice today.
還有…你今天很漂亮
-Oh,no. No, Ross, don't do this. -What?
不，羅斯，不要這樣 什麼？
I don't think us getting back together is a good idea.
我覺得我們不適合復合
I thought this might happen today.
我早就料到會這樣
I know the holidays can be rough...
我知道逢年過節特別難熬
and it's probably hard for you to be alone right now.
而且你一個人八成很辛苦
You're alone.
你也是一個人
No,I live with Phoebe.
不，我跟菲比住
I mean,you're alone-alone.
你就真的只有一個人
And it's just not the time for us. I'm sorry.
但這個時機真的不對，抱歉
Oh,well. Can't blame a guy for trying.
我總得試試看
And if anyone needs help pretending to like it...
要是有人不知道怎麼裝
I learned some things in acting class. Try rubbing your stomach.
我在表演課學過 你們可以摸摸肚子
Or saying, "Mmm."
或是說「嗯…」
Smiling.
還有微笑
I'm not gonna pay for those acting classes anymore.
我再也不花錢讓你去上表演課
Rachel,there you are. Let's serve that dessert already!
瑞秋，你回來了，快上甜點吧
Joey, you have to stop rushing me. You don't get any dessert.
喬伊，別再催我了 你知道嗎？罰你不准吃
Really?
是喔？
No,just kidding. I would never do that to you.
騙你的，我才不會虐待你
Okay, everybody, it's trifle time.
好，各位，酒果醬鬆糕時間到
So,Rach,this is a traditional English trifle,isn't it?
這是英式酒果醬鬆糕對吧？
-It sure is. -Wow.
一點也沒錯
So did you make it with beef or eggplant?
那你是加牛肉還是茄子？
-Beef. -I can't have any. I don't eat meat.
牛肉 我不能吃 你也知道我不吃肉
Monica, I want you to have the first taste.
摩妮卡，我要你第一個品嚐
Really?
是嗎？
Wait, you only got whipped cream.
等等，你只挖了鮮奶油
You gotta take a bite with all the layers.
你得挖到每一層
好
You dropped a pea.
等等，你掉了一顆豌豆
Well?
怎麼樣？
嗯…
It's good.
好好吃
Really? How good?
真的嗎？多好吃？
It's so good that I feel selfish...
好吃到...
about being the only one who's eating it.
我一個人吃會過意不去
I think we should have everyone taste how good it is.
我們應該讓每個人都享用
Especially Ross.
尤其是羅斯
This is so good that I'm gonna go enjoy it on the balcony.
真是太好吃了，我要去陽台吃
So that I can enjoy the view whilst I enjoy my dessert.
好邊看風景邊享用
I've gotta call my friend...
我要去房裡打電話
and tell her how good this is from Monica's room.
告訴我的朋友瑪麗有多好吃
I'll help dial.
我幫你撥號
I'm gonna go into the bathroom...
我要去浴室
so I can look at it in the mirror as I eat it.
好邊吃邊照鏡子
What was that all about? Does it not taste good?
這是怎麼回事？不好吃嗎？
-Let me try it. -No,no!
我吃吃看 什麼？不行
All gone!
都沒了
So good.
好好吃
Maybe Chandler has some left.
也許錢德還有剩
It tastes like feet.
味道好像洗腳水
I like it!
我喜歡
Are you kidding?
不是吧？
What's not to like? Custard, good.
有什麼不好？乳蛋糕？贊
Jam,good. Meat,good.
果醬？贊，牛肉？贊
So a bird just grabbed it...
一隻鳥就這樣一把搶過去…
and then tried to fly away with it...
想帶著它飛走
and then just dropped it on the street?
結果就掉到馬路上了？
If it's any consolation, before the bird dropped it...
對，不過值得安慰的是 掉下去之前...
he seemed to enjoy it.
它好像吃得很開心
Rachel,come here.
瑞秋，來一下
I was taking my Thanksgiving nap and I had another dream.
我剛剛小睡一覺，又夢到傑克
-Do I want to hear this? -I don't know,let's see.
菲比，我會想聽嗎？ 我不知道，你聽聽看
I dreamt we were getting married...
我夢到我們正要結婚
and he left because he had to go fight a fire.
結果他離開去救火
So I went to a nightclub and I saw him making out with a girl.
所以我去一家夜總會 卻看到他跟一個女的在親熱
Oh, my God, he dream-cheated on you!
天哪，他在夢裡背叛你
But then Jacques Cousteau came...
對，但這時賈克庫斯托出現
and he kicked his ass for betraying me.
幫我教訓了他一頓
So cool!
好酷喔
Then he took me diving and introduced me to his sea horse...
然後他帶我去潛水 跟我介紹他養的海馬
who was coming on to me. Please, that is not gonna happen.
它一直對我獻慇勤 但是怎麼可能
Boy,I'm glad I wore the big belt today.
幸好我今天繫了大皮帶
Five minutes ago,a line like that would have floored me.
5分鐘前 那種話會讓我神魂顛倒
But now,nothing. Well,not nothing. I am still a woman.
現在卻毫無作用… 一點點啦，我畢竟是女人
Ross? Let's go.
羅斯，來吧
Oh,yeah. About telling Mom and Dad...
關於告訴他們這件事
I was thinking about maybe writing a letter.
我考慮用寫信的
That's it. You've had your chance.
夠了，我給過你機會
What?
什麼？
Mom,Dad. Ross smoked pot in college.
媽，爸，羅斯大學哈過麻
What?
什麼？
You are such a tattletale!
你這個抓耙仔
Mom,Dad...
媽 爸
you remember that time you walked in my room...
記得你們在我房裡
and smelled marijuana?
聞到大麻的事嗎？
Yes.
記得
I told you it was Chandler...
我說是錢德
who was smoking the pot but...
在哈麻 其實…
it was me. I'm sorry.
是我，對不起
It was you?
是你？
And Dad, Chandler didn't melt your records.
爸，錢德沒把你的唱片燒壞
Ross did.
是羅斯干的
-Is that true? -And Dad...
是真的嗎？ 還有
you know that mailman that you got fired?
你害他被革職的郵差
He didn't steal your Playboys. Ross did.
他沒有偷你的花花公子 是羅斯偷的
Well, Hurricane Gloria didn't break the porch swing. Monica did!
前廊的鞦韆椅不是風雨弄壞的 是摩妮卡坐壞的
Ross hasn't worked at the museum for a year!
羅斯已經離開博物館1年了
Monica and Chandler are living together!
摩妮卡和錢德在同居
Ross married Rachel in Vegas! And got divorced! Again!
羅斯在賭城娶了瑞秋 然後又離婚了！
I love Jacques Cousteau!
我愛賈克庫斯托
I wasn't supposed to put beef in the trifle!
酒果醬鬆糕裡不該放牛肉的
I want to go!
我想走啦~~
That's a lot of information to get in 30 seconds.
這30秒真是高潮不斷啊
All right. Joey, if you want to leave, just leave.
好，喬伊，你想走就走吧
Rachel, no, you weren't supposed to put beef in the trifle.
瑞秋，這道甜點的確不能放肉
It did not taste good.
一點也不好吃
Phoebe,I'm sorry...
菲比，很抱歉
but I think Jacques Cousteau is dead.
賈克庫斯托已經死了
Monica, why you felt you had to hide the fact...
摩妮卡，我真不懂 你為何要隱瞞...
that you're in an important relationship is beyond me.
一段重要的感情
And we kind of figured about the porch swing.
其實鞦韆椅的事我們心裡有數
Ross.
羅斯
Drugs?
嗑藥？
Divorced again?
三度離婚？
What happened,son?
你是怎麼了？
I got tricked into all those things.
我都是遭人哄騙
Chandler, you've been Ross' best friend all these years...
錢德，你一直是羅斯的好朋友
stuck by him during the drug problems...
在他嗑藥時仍不放棄他
and now you've taken on Monica as well.
現在你又照顧起摩妮卡
Well,I don't know what to say.
我不知道該說什麼
You're a wonderful human being.
你真是個大好人
-Thank you! -No.
謝謝你 不
Thank you!
是謝謝你
Monica and Ross, I don't know what I'm gonna do about the two of you.
摩妮卡，羅斯 我真不知道該拿你們怎麼辦
I'll talk to them.
我會跟他們談
You guys, it was bananas...
各位，香蕉
cream and beef!
奶油加牛肉耶
I just cannot believe that you ate that so that I wouldn't feel bad.
你們居然因為怕我難過而吃掉
Well, actually, I didn't eat mine. It's still in the bathroom.
其實我沒吃，還放在浴室裡
No, I ate that.
沒有，我吃掉了
And we left ours in Monica's bedroom.
我們的在摩妮卡的房裡
Nope, got it and got yours too.
沒有，被我吃了，你的也是
Chandler, are you gonna stick with that bird story?
錢德 你還要死守你的鳥故事嗎？
It was a big bird. Swooped right in there.
那隻鳥很大，神准的衝過來
-Hi. -Oh,Janine.
吉寧
-It's not over,is it? -Yeah.
聚會還沒結束吧？ 結束了
We all got depressed. The holidays and everything, we're alone.
節日讓我們感到更孤單
Yeah,well,at least you have Joey.
至少你有喬伊
But Ross is really alone.
羅斯就真的是一個人
Well, you're always welcome here.
這裡永遠歡迎你
This is my mom and my dad.
這是我媽和我爸
-This is Janine. -Nice to meet you.
這位是吉寧 幸會…
-I think we've already met. -Really?
我們已經見過了 是嗎？
I live across the hall. You walked in on me when I was changing.
我住在對面 你在我換衣服時闖進來